let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the term for HTML elements with no content?",
        answer: "A. Closed elements",
        options: [
            "A. Closed elements",
            "B. Empty elements",
            "C. Void elements",  
            "D. Null elements" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What does lang attribute mean in the <html>?",
        answer: "C. Document language",
        options: [
            "A. Document title",
            "B. Document version", 
            "C. Document language",
            "D. Document author"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "How are name/value pairs formatted in the HTML attributes?",
        answer: "C. name is equal to the value inside the quotation marks ",
        options: [
            "A. name semicolon (;) value inside the quotation marks ", 
            "B. name colon(:) value inside the quotation marks ", 
            "C. name is equal to the value inside the quotation marks ", 
            "D. name is the value inside the quotation marks  "
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What is recommended for writing HTML tags?",
        answer: "C. Lowercase Tags",
        options: [
            "A. Uppercase Tags",
            "B. Title Case Tags",
            "C. Lowercase Tags",
            "D. Proper case Tags"

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the purpose of the <br> tag in HTML?",
        answer: "A. Defines a line break",
        options: [
            "A. Defines a line break", 
            "B. Creates a paragraph", 
            "C. Inserts an image", 
            "D. Highlights text" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What HTML element has a title attribute?",
        answer: "C. < p >",
        options: [
            "A. < html >", 
            "B. < body >", 
            "C. < p >", 
            "D. < br >" 
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the purpose of the title attribute in HTML?",
        answer: "D. Displays a tooltip",
        options: [
            "A. Defines a line break", 
            "B. Sets the document title", 
            "C. Highlights text", 
            "D. Displays a tooltip" 

        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What HTML element has a quote attribute?",
        answer: "A. < href >",
        options: [
            "A. < href >",
            "B. < src >",
            "C. < p >",
            "D. < br >"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Which HTML version does not require empty elements to be closed? ",
        answer: "B. HTML 5",
        options: [
            "A. HTML 4 ", 
            "B. HTML 5", 
            "C. XHTML", 
            "D. HTML 3.2"                
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Where are HTML attributes always specified?",
        answer: "D. In the start tag",
        options: [
            "A. In the opening tag", 
            "B. In the closing tag", 
            "C. In the end tag", 
            "D. In the start tag"                
        ]
    },
]